A Finding Aid to the Mary K. McGuigan and John F. McGuigan Jr. artists' letters collection, 1794-1938, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Mary K. McGuigan and John F. McGuigan Jr. Artists' Letters Collection, 1794-1938; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
  - Wolfe, John C., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
    One carte-de-visite portrait.